[theme music playing]
GENIE, MAKE A WISH
[guard] Someone's trying to
hack into the system.
What do they want? Do we know who it is?
Russia? North Korea?
[guard] They're trying to
figure that out. Hurry!
[intriguing music plays]
[system chimes]
[chuckles smugly]
ALARM
TEMPTATION
[gasps loudly]
[pills rattle]
[water pouring]
-You sleep okay?
-[gasps]
Let's kiss now.
[hesitates] Oh, I…
I need to plant those onions!
[pants]
[quirky music plays]
[groaning]
[shuddering]
Finished with the onions? Let's kiss.
[shudders] But I left
that thing over there.
So out of it,
I forgot to grab it. [whimpers]
-[wood thuds]
-[Iblis grunts]
-[gasps]
-You were looking for the coffin?
-Since you found it, let's kiss!
-Wait. Hold on. You can't rush it.
You know? It happens when it's right.
There are rules to this.
Rules around these sort of things.
-Okay?
-So what are they?
Yes, well, then about those rules, uh…
The first one's the weather.
Raindrops. It must rain.
It didn't rain yesterday.
It was the first time yesterday.
For the first kiss, rules can be
somewhat relaxed, even spontaneous,
but now that that's happened,
it must rain from now on.
We also need alcohol.
A drink before a kiss. That's when.
It's really that complicated?
Actually, way, way more complicated,
but I condensed it.
You can put the lid back on.
But you're not really a vampire, are you?
[keyboard clacking]
[mouse clicking]
[mysterious music plays]
[scoffs] Numbers have changed again.
That fucking psycho.
[mouse clicks]
What are these other funds?
KI KA-YOUNG
TOTAL ASSETS: 4,300,431,074 WON
CREDIT CARDS
MONTHLY PAY: 34,074,250
[mouse clicking]
CHEONGPUNGHO BANK
LUNCH BREAK
12 TO 1PM
[bell chimes]
Hey, Ki Ka-young and Choi Min-ji
were in your class at school?
-Yeah.
-Their bags are pricey.
They're both Hermès.
She just places it on the floor. [scoffs]
You two, hey. Two iced coffees, okay?
[groans] Every time we break for lunch.
-Great.
-Go on ahead. I'll take the usual.
Looking over your accounts, you should
set up a retirement savings plan.
A good way to set up for your future.
I don't need it.
There's no point in retirement.
[laughs] What do you mean,
there's no point?
It's just that she's not interested
in low-risk stocks.
She tends to invest more aggressively.
Of course, yes, I understand.
Okay. [chuckles]
That's good to know. Bo-gyeong,
the towel sets. Where are they?
-Oh.
-They're not prepared?
Bo-gyeong, why is it that you need
to be told every single thing?
I'll get the towels now.
Let's continue to prepare
for your retirement.
Let's discuss the advantages.
Your nest egg will…
[intriguing music plays]
The construction is complete. You just
need to decide when you want to move in.
-Do you like it?
-Yes, Papa.
-Daddy! Daddy!
-[squeals excitedly]
-Oh, yes, my sweet angel!
-[both chuckle]
Did our smart little princess
study hard today?
Of course! I'm so tired. I need a break.
You know, there was a new student
in school today.
-He's really cute.
-[Chang-sik] Oh, cute?
You found him cute? How cute is he?
-He looks like a little king.
-Oh.
-So I asked where he lives.
-Yeah?
-He said that big house we wondered about.
-The one that a way?
-Yep.
-They live in that house?
Let's go see them and bring them
our good rice cakes.
We have to welcome them to our town.
[both] Ah!
[pop music playing faintly over TV]
[gasps]
So the kissing rules
are actually accurate?
-[door opens]
-[gasps]
Genie, tell me what tomorrow's weather
is going to be like.
The weather? How would I know that?
It's a touchy subject, okay?
What are you so riled up about?
I'm just asking about the weather.
Hey, Genie,
what's the weather like tomorrow?
[AI Genie] Tomorrow, in Cheongpung,
it's going to be a clear and sunny day.
That's right. You should try asking it
something. It knows everything.
[Iblis scoffs] Okay, other Genie.
What does Ki Ka-young most want to know?
[AI Genie] Here's a list of
Ki Ka-young's recent search history.
Rainmaking rites, artificial rain,
the alcoholic content of beer,
cool-toned lip tints,
express delivery action.
Rainmaking rites, rainmaking rites,
rainmaking rites…
What the hell have you done, you idiot?
…rainmaking rites.
Find out how much rain
is expected this week.
I already looked it up because the cherry
blossom festival starts very soon.
-We've got clear skies most of the week!
-Ugh! Why?
[trunk thuds]
How about next week?
Uh, the spring rainy season
probably starts next week after Monday.
-Why is Monday excluded?
-You want me to exclude it?
Can you really do that?
-Since you're a fairytale creature?
-I don't have that range.
I could recite a devotion. [laughs]
Not the helpful type.
Why don't you put down the wrench
and tell me what this is about?
[Sade exhales nervously]
-You see something there?
-Yes, today I'm pretty.
[Iblis humming]
[stops humming]
So pretty.
[breath trembles]
Beautiful.
[panting]
It's like the town got short on cash.
They couldn't invite some bigwig
for the jamboree?
-[metal clangs]
-Wha-- Oh!
Put that knife down!
I'm so pretty.
All day I've been pretty.
Goodness gracious, young lady!
We have mirrors all over the house!
[whimsical music plays]
[Sade] This isn't your fault, Master.
Psychopaths are known to have
narcissistic personality traits.
Is that so? Oh, that's good to know.
I thought I made her pretty somehow.
I mean, I really brought it that night.
[sighs] Why did I put it all out there
at that very moment?
What are you going on about?
You must put it all out there!
Kissing is a good first step
towards corruption.
Right. That's how I used to do it.
[sighs] Though
it's been a thousand years.
It's really been the first kiss since
that long ago. Oh, I was so nervous.
[chuckles, sighs]
My goodness,
it makes me feel bad for Ejllael.
You know, Master, he works nonstop
in hopes of slitting your throat.
He goes through all that effort when just
one kiss has you digging your grave.
-Although, first kiss in a millennium?
-What's the problem?
Shouldn't you have gone to
a dentist first? Ugh, so gross. Ew!
-Ugh!
-A dentist?
What's that?
[dramatic music plays]
[assistant] Any discomfort,
raise your hand.
We haven't started yet.
-Now, open wide.
-[shudders]
[drill whirring]
-[Iblis whimpers]
-Let's try to hang in there.
[Iblis yelping loudly]
[yelping loudly]
So, you don't have any money,
or any form of ID?
No one bothered to get this info
before the cleaning?
He said the owner of the repair shop
was a good friend of his.
Ki Ka-young? Aside from me,
she has no other friends. Oh!
-You're from the Middle East?
-Min-ji?
-Oh! Min-ji!
-[squeals]
[Iblis] Oh.
You ate gamja-tang before. I saw you
eat gamja-tang at her favorite joint.
[Iblis laughs]
So because you watched me
eat gamja-tang one time,
you think you get a free service?
[Ka-young] No money?
[Min-ji] It's crazy, right?
Can you believe this guy?
He doesn't even have any kind of ID.
He just keeps saying his name…
[laughs] …is Lee Beu-li.
What kind of name is that?
It's so ridiculous.
What else could I say to him
at that point?
How am I supposed to trust anything
about this guy?
I can say one thing for sure.
He's not a real man.
[Min-ji] Of course not!
There's no way he could be!
No real man would date someone
when he's flat-out broke.
I was told to raise these when I'm feeling
uneasy. I'm feeling very uneasy right now.
Ugh, you really suck.
Dr. Choi, we got to get set up
at the festival.
All right, let's go.
Can't you tell he's using you?
Get it together!
Miss Ki, take care of yourself!
[scoffs] He has a pretty face.
And he's tall,
and he has a nice voice too.
What else does he have going for him?
[Ka-young sighs]
I had to get my teeth cleaned
for the rainy season.
When I become a pro gamer,
I'll pay you ba-- [sighs]
Pro gamer?
You haven't won a single game against the
local kids, and you think you're a gamer?
All right.
-[comical music plays]
-[sighs]
Only one side of my face.
I took that beating well. [chuckles]
[mimics engine revving]
-[remote clicks]
-[car engine starts]
Whoa! What the… [gasps]
Miss Ki! Check the tire pressure,
would you?
[Ka-young] Okay!
[mimicking engine revving]
You having a beer?
Yeah, that's right.
And with the engine on,
you're at the wheel of a car?
Mm-hmm. Yes, I'm behind the wheel.
Engine? Which one is that?
Okay, sir, go ahead
and blow into this now.
What is it? A pipe?
[chuckles] Come on.
[blowing]
-Yes, go.
-More.
-[officers] More, more, more, more!
-[horn honking]
-[rapid beeping]
-[sustained honking]
[woman] Hello, my homies!
Hey! It's Da-jin of Sky Farm Life.
I'm coming live to you from
the Cheongpung Cherry Blossom Festival.
Let's start by raiding
the For Daughter Strawberry stand.
What happens when strawberries
are stuck in traffic?
-[man] What?
-A berry jam.
[both laughing]
"Strawberry jam!"
See that? There's a reason
these things don't work out.
-Great. Good. [continues indistinctly]
-Yeah.
[Min-ji] Say "Ah." That's right.
Really good.
[sucks breath] Let's try opening wider.
A little more.
"Ah." Wider. "Ah, ah."
Hello there. We're Cheongpungho Bank.
We're having a promotion for savings
account. Come by for a consultation.
Hello.
[in Arabic] Where is the bathroom?
Is the subway station close by?
Without cilantro, please.
[in English] What's he saying?
Are you Arabic? Is that it?
Before, you were speaking Korean properly.
[Iblis] Hmm?
-He's asking to leave the cilantro out.
-What?
[chuckles] Arabic was all the rage
when I was in school,
so I learned it as my second language.
I can try speaking to him.
[clears throat]
[in Arabic] My name is Oh Gyeong-yeol,
a police officer
from the Republic of Korea.
Sir, you have violated the traffic laws--
[snaps fingers]
[in English] Get over here now!
You said I just had to talk in Arabic.
Oh, well, it worked for me,
but that was 100 years ago.
Go ahead, I'll take care of things.
-You shit!
-[whimpers]
[upbeat music playing over speakers]
Oh Pan-geum! Buy that,
it's yummy. That one.
Why are you eating a bag of raw tofu?
This is what you eat
after a visit to the slammer.
Pan-geum, get black goat extract.
Black goat, okay? For longevity.
How would I afford that?
Why don't you buy it for me then?
Sorry, I can't afford it either.
I can only make suggestions.
I can't tell if you're a rascal,
or just poor, and good for nothing.
-[squeaking]
-Oh, my!
-Hmm?
-Hey, hey, look over there!
[toy squeaking]
My goodness! That puppy's bopping!
How wonderful, don't you think?
-Whoa! Wow! What is that? [laughs]
-[vendor] Come and see.
-How adorable!
-Super cool!
[laughs]
[Iblis] Wow, it's walking
but somehow stays in the same spot.
How does it do that?
[toy squeaking]
[Iblis] At least her joints
are in good shape.
-Oh!
-Hi there. So sorry, okay?
What's wrong?
I heard about something called fireworks.
-Do you know when and where?
-[chuckles]
Ah, the fireworks?
They'll go off after the sun sets.
Uh, over there.
Those are the best views.
-Have a good time.
-Ah.
The best views are there.
[humming]
[music continues over speakers]
[thug] Ta-da! That's it! Uh…
Ah, shit. That asshole seemed like
he was loaded. All he had was this.
[sighs] This is nothing!
Look over there at those motherfuckers
with no decency.
This is our turf.
What are you doing on it?
Oh, we're here for the cherry blossom
festival. The spring breeze is good.
This cherry blossom festival
is part of our turf.
You didn't see us bumming around
at your salmon festival.
Well, then, you're welcome
to come to next year's one.
Want a personal invite, huh?
Yeah. You can get a new arm
while you're here.
The prosthetics in Cheongpung
are exceptional.
You're gonna need it.
[thugs grunting]
-Whoa.
-What the hell?
[sighs] Phew, what a relief!
She would've beaten me up again.
-Huh? Who's this stupid prick?
-[blows]
-Hey, you. What gang do you belong to?
-Huh?
-[thug 2] Why doesn't he answer?
-Hey, let's fucking wipe him out!
-[thugs yelling]
-[gasps]
-[gasps, whimpers]
[Iblis] My, oh, my. [scoffs]
How about some flowers?
[upbeat music plays]
[thugs yelling, grunting]
[grunts, exclaims]
[both grunting]
[fireworks exploding]
[Pan-geum] Those are so bright
and beautiful!
[Heung-rye] My gosh. How dazzling!
-Oh.
-Oh, my.
Oh, how mesmerizing.
[indistinct chatter]
[Pan-geum] Oh, my goodness.
That's… that's Ka-young's name,
isn't it?
"Heart. You. Live, fuck"?
What? I don't get it.
So that asshole does have money.
So you're saying girls love
to be spoken to that way?
Yes, sir. If you believe in me,
I promise I'll never steer you wrong.
They all fall for it.
Now it's just a waiting game
until she's corrupted. [cackling]
I like that.
[upbeat music continues]
KI KA-YOUNG
FUCK OFF
[sighs] That ass.
I have that exact same thought
when I see Iblis.
It's good to know you can relate, Miss Ki.
Why are you here?
You don't need repairs, you can fly.
Everyone's at the festival,
so this neighborhood's a ghost town.
-I thought I'd visit so we can talk alone.
-What do you have to say then?
No point asking for your feather.
[laughs] No, it's yours.
What's your species anyway?
Yorkshire Terriers and Chihuahuas
are a kind.
There are also angels, humans,
devils and Genies. So what one are you?
Let's say I'm his servant. You saw
my wings, so you should know I'm an angel.
Oh, an angel? Clarify that for me
since you have black wings.
You're the food bank volunteer.
I've been thinking this over.
It's strange that every time
you come with meals, a life ends.
Older people die.
I suppose you could maybe see it that way.
Mmm. Here's another perspective.
I visit the elderly
who are already at death's door.
It's normal some end up dying.
[tense music plays]
I see.
By the way, several of your buildings
are located within just a few blocks
of this repair shop.
You also don't bother hiding
your true identity.
-Are you trying to keep an eye on me?
-Oh? That's correct.
I work on his mandate, to be more precise.
What's that? His mandate?
"If Iblis decides to bow his head
to a human, you'll then…
slit your brother's throat."
Thrilling, isn't it?
That's why I'll do whatever it takes
to ensure that you don't fall for Iblis.
It's too late.
[tense music continues]
What?
The repair store is closing up.
Ah. [chuckles]
It's that time already? Hmm.
But why the sudden tone shift?
Let's see. It could be that psychopaths
can't hide their irritation.
Or because you're trying to kill my Genie
before I do. Or maybe…
it's because I've fallen for him.
Which reason is it?
[tense music continues]
[Ejllael] I knew it.
I was right about her.
[sighs]
Did something happen, sir?
-I found all these--
-Get rid of all these books!
-Psychopath? How about deranged?
-[books clattering]
I should have known it was too easy.
[sighs] The two remaining wishes
could be at risk if she's this way.
I should have taken my scythe with me.
I mean, she spoke to me like a child!
Can you believe the audacity?
-That's so disrespectful.
-Mm-hmm.
You do look very young, for your age.
[scoffs]
[buttons clacking]
Did you see the fireworks?
I did the big ones.
-Weren't they cool?
-Uh, why pick those ones?
-[gasps] No!
-[video game announcer] K.O.
Hey, are you bamboozling me or what?
-So, you were behind the fireworks?
-Uh-huh.
[sighs] I wondered
what maniac would do that.
Mani-- What?
[sighs] Hey.
-Where do you live? Show me the way, kid.
-[Min-ji] And where do you live?
Show me the way.
What?
Overall, psychopaths
hurt others, okay?
To get what they want.
But our dear Ka-young,
she is a bit different.
Her grandma and the whole neighborhood
rallied together to raise her.
Though she may not feel guilt,
there are basic boundaries
she has learned to keep.
Mmm.
[clicks tongue, inhales] Okay, so what?
So I'm saying
that I'm watching you, asshole.
Ka-young has to keep
within her boundaries.
And I keep her safe from any threats.
Psychologically… [grunting]
…or physically.
I'm her knight in shining armor.
You are, aren't you?
All this time, I was thinking
you were a girl. Oh, my gosh. [chuckles]
This is on the house. [chuckles]
[both laughing]
[soft music plays]
[chuckles]
-[laughing]
-What are you laughing about?
That's the funniest thing I've heard
in 1,000 years.
-[both laughing]
-[Min-ji] 1,000 years?
What are you talking about?
You came to a seafood restaurant
just because a guy is with us?
-That's annoying.
-I only walked in when I saw you here.
I'll drop Min-ji off.
Go ahead and I'll see you at home.
Why don't I take her home?
We've gotten really close.
-Wait, Ka-young!
-[laughs] Excuse me, sir?
-Is there anything else you need?
-Mmm…
-Charity?
-What?
[amusing music plays]
Min-ji didn't leave any cash.
And, well, I… [claps]
I have no money at all. [laughing]
[woman] Oh!
[both laughing]
Oh, I know what that is. I got it.
-[line rings]
-This the police?
I'm turning myself in.
[distant siren wailing]
You dined and dashed? Huh?
[sighs] This is so unfair!
I didn't really dine. I didn't even dash.
Will you shut it?
Why call me to bail you out? And what
about the other one, huh? The angel?
[sighs] You don't know the whole story.
Ejllael and I are not only different,
we're also on very bad terms.
You and I are also on very bad terms.
[sighs] Why are you lowering your voice?
Even for Satan,
this isn't a laughing matter.
Ejllael and I fought a long war
against each other.
It was a devastating war.
Why did you two go to war?
-[thunderclap]
-[dramatic orchestral music plays]
[Iblis] He created the angels from light.
And the genies were made
from smokeless fire.
The genies created from fire
became increasingly arrogant.
They had ambitions
to become greater than Him.
In his rage, He sent the angels
and ordered them to exterminate us.
[water gurgling]
[dramatic orchestral music continues]
The angels came down and began
slaughtering all of the genies on earth.
And Ejllael, he led the charge.
The war lasted almost 300 years.
I lost most of my brothers in the fight.
You turned a petty fight
into a 300-year war?
I've barely seen my brothers since then.
I had defied His orders, so as punishment,
I was sent to Hell.
And when I was released, I got stuck in
a lamp for 1,000 years. So, you know.
Where are your surviving brothers now?
I don't know.
Out in the world, in some pot or a lamp.
Living out the rest of their days.
[Iblis] They might be controlling sleep.
Or tending to the garden of souls.
[water gurgling]
-Or even controlling the rain.
-[rain pattering]
Wait. Controlling the rain?
-Huh?
-Can you find the brother who does that?
-Tell him--
-He's moved to somewhere unknown.
Oh! Sade is calling out. I got to go.
-[pants]
-[whooshing]
Sade isn't looking for you. I can tell.
-[Iblis] Phew.
[captivating music plays]
Wow.
[tool whirring]
Hey, miss. Does the owner
of this car live nearby?
Yes.
Total crypto king, huh?
I used to have one of these.
It's a 2024 model.
[tool whirring]
Oh, hey, you! Stop. I said patch the tire.
Why are you removing it?
You need to change it.
Have you even disclosed all of this?
It's a lot. Every customization?
What are you, a cop?
Why would I report that?
Hey, put it back on.
-Where do you live, huh?
-[scoffs] What makes you ask that?
You got the hots for me?
I just have this sense
that you'll die on the way there.
-[scoffs]
-These wheels were customized for you?
The tire sizes are wrong.
If I just fix the hole,
it won't last an hour
before it breaks away.
I've explained it to you now.
Call a tow truck to take it out of here.
I refuse to fix it.
You treat your clients this way?
Hey, come here.
[footsteps approaching]
[whimsical music plays]
[exhales contentedly] Is everything okay?
Did you just drink that?
There's still a lot left.
These are for us, aren't they?
[sighs] That's why they keep going fast.
Oh, so what were you saying?
Uh, I need the tow truck's number, please.
0-1-0-6-3-4-2--
Please wait. I couldn't catch that.
[chuckles nervously]
You hit him or something?
[burps, exhales]
[bubble pops]
Whoa.
6-3-4… [sighs]
You're ruining the vibe!
This isn't a little kid's birthday party!
I'll report everything. I'm so very sorry.
-Thank you.
-[Sade] Where are you going?
-Why is he leaving? Don't go.
-Oh, shit!
[staff] Hello, ma'am.
Hello, ma'am.
Who's in charge of the display here?
Tell me, who's in charge here?
-Uh… Oh, she's here!
-[pants] I'm here. I'm sorry.
I ran quickly.
I had to just go out for a second.
I'm having tummy issues again. [laughs]
What makes you think that's an excuse
to leave your station?
We all get sick when we get to our age.
You want to keep your job,
just do it! Is that hard?
-[staff] Uh…
-I won't put up with this.
Ms. Jung Yeong-sun, what did you just say?
I won't put up with it anymore.
I'm fed up with you so I'm quitting.
Your behavior lately has been crazy.
Have you let that promotion
get to your head?
Ms. Jung Yeong-sun!
I don't know how you got that promotion,
but who do you think you are
treating people like this?
There are rumors
that you're taking bribes.
-That true? You think we're stupid?
-Okay, okay.
[Yeong-sun breathing heavily]
[Im-seon breathing heavily]
I was such a fool.
How could I ask to be a branch manager
at this age?
Everyone looks down on me,
and I'm bad at the job.
-[breath trembling]
-[chuckles softly]
I should've become manager sooner.
[pants] Hey, you! Here.
Here's my second wish.
Take me to 20 years ago.
I want to be manager then.
[gasps] If I became branch manager then,
how much would I have made?
[laughs] Mmm.
[chuckles softly]
Then back we go?
To 20 years before?
[chuckles]
[enchanting choral music plays]
[music fades]
BRANCH MANAGER KANG IM-SEON
CHEONGPUNGHO MART
-[gasps]
-[cell phone ringing]
Once you walk through that door,
it will be 20 years in the past,
and you'll still work as the manager.
-[chuckles softly]
-[cell phone ringing]
Yes, hello?
[ominous music plays]
Why are you here alone? Where's your dad?
He said he was going to get you.
Well, Papa has work to do.
It's been a while.
Do you still drink chamomile tea?
Yeah, I continue to be a psychopath,
so caffeine's not for me.
[laughs]
Some people never change.
I thought you'd at least ask
what I'm doing here.
I live here now, with my wife and kid.
We just bought a house.
You put this area on our radar.
I've never told you
exactly where I happen to live.
It's not every day that a fellow alum
opens her own garage.
Oh.
Anyway, it's nice to see you again.
Looks like you're doing well.
And the garage is okay?
[Ka-young] This is true joy.
[Sade growling]
[growling]
[gentle music plays]
This house is the same
as it was 20 years ago.
Except for you.
[rock thudding]
[breath trembling]
[sighs]
In 20 years, you're going to grow up
to be really pretty.
So try not to hurt yourself.
Scars last forever.
[gasps]
-Whoa, what is it?
-Oh, weird memory just resurfaced.
[Iblis] Hmm?
I promised Grandma
to never speak with strangers.
-Go away!
-Ow!
-No!
-Whoa, are you okay?
[sighs]
You haven't changed at all,
as odd as ever.
-[laughing]
-[sighs]
[Sade] "You haven't changed at all,
as odd as ever." [laughs mockingly]
[scoffs]
He was sleazy as hell. Tell me again,
how did you cut your head?
[Iblis] Tsk.
Who do you think did it? [sighs]
Twenty years before, she was even worse.
Did you go to the past
to grant a wish for someone?
-[Iblis] Hmm.
-[rain pattering]
-[thunder rumbling]
-[Iblis] Hmm?
[gasps softly]
[gasps loudly]
[gasps]
[brushing vigorously]
[ominous music plays]
[thunderclap]
That… that'll be 13 bucks.
[beeps]
[cashier] I do need to see
your ID for alcohol.
[fighting noises]
OUT OF ORDER
[chiptune music playing
over arcade machine]
Miss Ki. Is something wrong?
The rain has come.
Have a good night.
[thunder rumbling]
[yelling] Where the hell is he?
-[rain stops]
-[thunder stops]
Why? Why is it doing this?
Why is it stopping?
It's rainy season!
Where were you? It rained tonight!
Do you know how long I searched
the neighborhood looking for you?
Jeez. Hey. You took
a rock this big and you--
Wow. I mean, I heard you were "odd,"
but that's just--
You're changing the subject
as a defense tactic.
By the way, who's the dope that went
and visited you at the garage?
I heard you were kiki-ing together.
You can kiss me or beat me up.
But you can't do both, you kissing maniac!
That right? Then I'm beating you up.
-Get over here.
-Hey, wait.
-You're my master.
-[dog barks]
Shush, you! We're talking right now!
Listen, treat your Genie with care.
-Be nice to me, okay?
-[barking]
I told you to shush!
Jeez, why do all the dogs here
bark like that when they see you?
-[barking]
-They're worried I might take them in.
They rely on reading human feelings
and expressions, and I don't have any.
Look, you! I have no desire
to take you in!
[barking]
[pants, growls]
[continues barking]
Sade!
[sniffing]
[mysterious music plays]
[dog whines]
I'm a spirit of the lamp, a Genie.
[sped-up] I'll grant
three wishes. Make them.
No bringing back the dead,
no traveling to the future.
Anything other than that,
your wish is my command.
[normal voice] First, though,
and pass this on
to the other dogs in the neighborhood.
Stop barking at Ka-young.
If they keep barking even one more time,
I'll turn every last one of you
into a cat.
Go on, say it.
[barking, growling]
[mouthing] Ki Ka-young.
[continues barking]
[growls, meows]
MUTT (AGE 7), MAY 16, 2024
MADE ITS FIRST WISH
TO BECOME A PERSON, WITH SPECIFICS
CHARMING MIDDLE-AGED MAN IN HIS 40S
WHO LOOKS LIKE DANIEL HENNEY
Wow. That's not a face you often see here.
[chuckles] Are they shooting?
You know how I was sad
about losing my eyesight?
-Yeah.
-I'm not worried anymore. [chuckles]
-[chuckles] Let's go then.
-Yeah.
[woman chuckles] Wow.
[upbeat music playing]
[women gasping]
I'm so hungry.
Galbi?
Sounds good. Okay, let's go.
-[gasps]
-[passerby gasps]
Nice hair, nice suit. So handsome.
He's coming toward us.
Do you have makeup in your bag?
[sniffs]
[sniffing]
[woman gasps]
[continues sniffing]
[comical music plays]
-[gasps]
-[man] Gross, what's he doing?
[woman] He must be crazy!
-[barks]
-[woman] Disgusting!
I've heard the handsome ones
are either dogs or gay.
Well, with how he's acting…
he's clearly a dog.
[objects thudding, clattering]
[Ejllael sighs]
You don't have any water here.
Eat the food tomorrow morning.
[groans, mutters indistinctly]
What?
I don't like the food you give us.
It tastes stale.
[laughs]
Oh, you're saying
it has no flavor. [chuckles]
I could've been heavier-handed
with the salt.
[strained laughing]
It was a joke. [chuckling]
What else does life have in store for me?
Mmm. I'm tired
of that question. [chuckles]
There's one thing I know for certain.
I'll be saving on the cost of salt.
[foreboding music plays]
[tool whirring]
-[blows]
-[cell phone vibrating]
Hi, Grandma.
Ka-young, sweetheart,
you're not seeing things again, are you?
You're taking your medication
and not missing any doses?
Yeah, I'm taking medication
every day. Why?
And if you have any wishes,
you'll tell me about them, right?
-I'll get them for you.
-Wha-- Wishes?
I found this notebook in your room.
What is it? Did…
Did you have a crush on Daniel Henney?
You can… see that?
She's able to see that?
[Iblis] Huh.
Was it always visible to everyone else?
You're seriously asking me that?
[sighs] This stupid magic
is too complicated.
This isn't going to work.
We need a place that's safe and private
to hide the notebook.
Your lamp. No one but you and Sade
are able to get into the lamp, right?
[inhales sharply] If they really
wanted to, Ejllael or Irem could.
You can't enter alone.
Which means it's safe.
What does it look like inside?
Is it warm and cozy?
[clicks tongue, sighs]
It's dismal.
[clicks tongue]
Mmm.
You get it now? Can you picture
how lonely I was in here?
I was trapped for 983 years.
I'm sorry, but I don't feel loneliness.
Are you able to feel sorry?
Of course not.
I say the word "sorry" to be considerate.
Min-ji told me that.
You know what consideration is?
Yes. That one's easy.
As long as I'm honest, it's fine.
For example, I might say something like
this. That relative of yours said that
if you bow your head to a righteous human,
he'll slit your throat.
Ejllael, that asshole!
[scoffs] You think that was considerate?
That's a big threat.
I can't believe it. [exhales]
I'm not scaring you at all.
If I'm being honest,
I don't know what fear is.
Grandma said apathy
is the worst quality in a person.
My grandma is a safety net to my apathy,
and if that safety net…
were to disappear, then I might become
my most violent self.
I'm preparing for that possibility.
You probably know that from spying.
[Iblis] You want to make your death
seem natural.
[hesitates] Of course I know.
It'll be as close
to a natural death as possible.
Like some equipment malfunction at sea.
But what's the point if you don't have
any affection for humans?
Growing up, I learned I'm a stone
in everybody's shoe.
I make people uncomfortable.
So when I remove myself, the stone's gone.
For Grandma's sake.
Kill me if you're going to, and make it
quick. Don't get your throat slit.
Ejllael?
The more I see that angel,
the more he sucks.
-You can't ever lose to him, okay?
-So you're going to take my side now?
-I can't do that?
-No, you can't!
If you help me win, then… [sighs]
When I…
kill you…
Be so strange.
We're beyond strange already.
We're both considered anti-social.
Why do I get the finger-pointing
when everybody loves you?
So what was even the point
of bringing us back together again?
You're right.
That's something
I should've thought about.
At least you seem to understand.
Let's bring furniture. All right.
We'll put the table and chairs
I made in the workshop here.
[sighs heavily]
[lively orchestral music plays]
[whooshing]
They look like you bought them in a store.
I can't believe you created these.
No matter which way
you look at them, the details…
Will you stop talking?
Furniture count, two.
A rug over here would be nice,
wouldn't it?
[scoffs]
Closer, closer.
[Iblis] Hmm?
[automated voice]
Starting the cleaning cycle.
[Iblis] What's this for?
Is it used to fix things,
or maybe to destroy things?
That's up to you, I guess.
[lid thuds]
Hey!
You can't re-enter if you go that way.
It'll take longer than 1,000 years.
That thing.
[vacuum whirring]
[chuckles sheepishly]
[Ka-young] It looks
a little bit nicer now.
I'm feeling better.
Let's talk about Ms. Im-seon.
She could have wished for anything.
She chose a promotion.
What's with the supermarket
that makes her unable to leave?
Humans are like that.
They don't have the confidence to be kings
outside of their own castles.
They only want to rule what they already
know, so that's what they wish for.
It's one of the most
pathetic human traits.
And the reason I hate them all.
-[book thuds]
-[scoffs]
[Ka-young] Mmm. Mmm.
He knows so much,
but understands so little.
Humans hate you too, you know.
[nervously] Ah, so that's the other
use for that. [chuckles nervously]
If I kill you on behalf of all humans,
would that ensure I go to Heaven?
You think you would end there?
He'd give you Heaven if you asked.
Come here, now!
Come on, show yourself!
-I'm going to get you! Get here!
-Ooh! [laughs]
-[Ka-young shouting indistinctly]
-[Iblis laughing]
-[Ka-young] Get over here.
-No way.
[indistinct shouting]
[muffled shouting]
Where is that weird sound coming from?
[muffled shouting continues]
What's this? The sound's coming from here?
-This a radio?
-[muffled shouting]
[Heung-rye] Pan-geum, you here?
Pan-geum, are you home?
-Hello!
-Yes, Seongnim!
-[rumbling]
-[Pan-geum] Whoa!
You came all this way
when it's raining so much?
[Iblis breathing heavily]
The rain.
I heard her say it's raining.
[soft music plays]
That sounds right, doesn't it?
Is there alcohol here?
I could get it.
Couldn't we both go together?
Be quicker if we do.
-Do you have money for the alcohol?
-You pay with this.
-[Pan-geum sobbing]
-Oh, as collateral?
-I wanted to tell you as soon as I heard.
-Grandma?
[sobbing]
Grandma! Why are you crying?
What happened?
-[sobs] What do we do?
-Why is my granny crying?
We just heard
Mr. Kim, the craftsman, has died.
He was the man, the man who taught you
how to carve wood.
Okay, but why is Grandma crying?
A man passed away, so she's sad.
She's sad because he was her friend.
This is exactly why, you know,
why you get called a psychopath.
-Seongnim!
-Oh?
Oh! Oh, my! Oh, no!
My goodness.
Death makes it all seem meaningless.
[both sobbing]
[Heung-rye] It brings out all of the…
all of the tears! [wails]
-[indistinct chatter]
-[people crying]
[Pan-geum sniffles]
[Pan-geum] Oh, my. Oh, goodness.
It's so awful. I can't bear it.
The world casts away someone like him.
[Chang-sik sighs] Well, even so,
he passed comfortably,
as if he were sleeping.
That must be considered a good death.
That's a myth. There's no such thing
as having a good death.
You kids have no idea,
you still have so many years before you.
[Pan-geum] I have no fear
when it comes to dying.
But, when I… I think of Ka-young…
[sobbing]
I worry that my heart will stop beating
because of…
a heart attack.
Or what if I have a stroke?
What if I get cancer and diabetes,
and end up with dementia?
Oh! I would only burden her!
How will she ever take care of me?
Why would you say something like that?
It was in that moment, I realized
she read the exact same articles I did.
"The Rapidly Growing Aging Society."
"Getting Ready for Age-Related Illnesses."
"Medical Tomorrow."
If Grandma dies, I have to die too.
Yet, Grandma, she wants to live
a long and pain-free life.
So, what are you saying?
I am ready to make my second wish.
I want Grandma young.
So make Pan-geum my exact age.
That's it.
This will be the second wish.
[gasps softly]
[upbeat dance music playing]
[music continues]
[music ends]